(Raj:)What do you mean?
(Sheldon:)How many women
have you had dates with?
(Raj:)Eleven.
(Sheldon:)How many of those women did you think
would become your perfect companion?
(Raj:)Eleven.
(Raj:)Wait. Do I count the 200-pound
Sailor Moon girl
(Raj:)that Howard and I had
a threesome with at Comic-Con?
(Sheldon:)Sure.
I'll stick with 11.
She liked Howard better.
(Sheldon:)Well, now do you see the problem?
(Raj:)Maybe. I...
I don't know.
It's late, I... I should...
I should go.
(Raj:)Look, I do get what you're saying.
(Raj:)Instead of desperately clinging
to any woman who will go out with me,
(Raj:)I need to work
on my fear of being alone.
(Sheldon:)I was trying to suggest
chemical castration, but...